[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Does it weigh heavily on your shoulders that you were a personal witness to these three extraordinary things?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "weigh", "heavily", "on", "your", "shoulders", "that", "you", "were", "a", "personal", "witness", "to", "these", "three", "extraordinary", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well I don't considered it dead because I've been doing this for 67 years and I covered a lot of big stories and it's just what I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "do", "n't", "considered", "it", "dead", "because", "I", "'ve", "been", "doing", "this", "for", "67", "years", "and", "I", "covered", "a", "lot", "of", "big", "stories", "and", "it", "'s", "just", "what", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "When you head the shots go out what was your first reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "head", "the", "shots", "go", "out", "what", "was", "your", "first", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "You know, I don't know how fast I reacted because it was such an instantaneous bedlam (ph) there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "fast", "I", "reacted", "because", "it", "was", "such", "an", "instantaneous", "bedlam", "(", "ph", ")", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Now there were three shots that you heard, you began to speak to witnesses, you grabbed to sort of make shift pencil and paper from a little boy I think that you saw right?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "there", "were", "three", "shots", "that", "you", "heard", ",", "you", "began", "to", "speak", "to", "witnesses", ",", "you", "grabbed", "to", "sort", "of", "make", "shift", "pencil", "and", "paper", "from", "a", "little", "boy", "I", "think", "that", "you", "saw", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "But you saw him actually apprehended?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "saw", "him", "actually", "apprehended", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Yes I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "So, you witnessed the arrest of Lee Harvey Oswald and then you say Jack Ruby shoot him dead?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "witnessed", "the", "arrest", "of", "Lee", "Harvey", "Oswald", "and", "then", "you", "say", "Jack", "Ruby", "shoot", "him", "dead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well that was a couple days later and I had known that there had been all kinds of threats to the police department that they were going to take this communist SOB they said, and I just thought they'd move him during the night.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "that", "was", "a", "couple", "days", "later", "and", "I", "had", "known", "that", "there", "had", "been", "all", "kinds", "of", "threats", "to", "the", "police", "department", "that", "they", "were", "going", "to", "take", "this", "communist", "SOB", "they", "said", ",", "and", "I", "just", "thought", "they", "'d", "move", "him", "during", "the", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lee Harvey Oswald", "Jack Ruby"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "YNESWORTH: Well you know, I understand them, I don't agree with them at all.", "answer_tokens": ["YNESWORTH", ":", "Well", "you", "know", ",", "I", "understand", "them", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "agree", "with", "them", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "We're you very quickly aware that he was unlikely to survive?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "you", "very", "quickly", "aware", "that", "he", "was", "unlikely", "to", "survive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "As soon as I walked in to trauma room one and saw him -- Mrs. Kennedy was on the left inside of the room.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "soon", "as", "I", "walked", "in", "to", "trauma", "room", "one", "and", "saw", "him", "--", "Mrs.", "Kennedy", "was", "on", "the", "left", "inside", "of", "the", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Did you say anything to them?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "say", "anything", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "EAD: Well, I talked to her.", "answer_tokens": ["EAD", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "talked", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "The moment when he was pronounced dead, I mean that's a chilling moment, isn't it for you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "when", "he", "was", "pronounced", "dead", ",", "I", "mean", "that", "'s", "a", "chilling", "moment", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Well yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Were you -- how would you describe your state?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "--", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "your", "state", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I think we kicked in to a routine management of a coma patient.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "kicked", "in", "to", "a", "routine", "management", "of", "a", "coma", "patient", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Is there a single day that goes by in your life when you don't think of this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "single", "day", "that", "goes", "by", "in", "your", "life", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "think", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "There are aren't many that go by because something reminds you one way or the other.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "are", "n't", "many", "that", "go", "by", "because", "something", "reminds", "you", "one", "way", "or", "the", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "It never stop, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "never", "stop", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "But I don't it will ever stop.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "do", "n't", "it", "will", "ever", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Kerry let me start with you, you were just four years old and I know you don't really have any memory of that awful day but in terms of the legacy of JFK, what would you think it should be as a member of the family?", "question_tokens": ["Kerry", "let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "you", "were", "just", "four", "years", "old", "and", "I", "know", "you", "do", "n't", "really", "have", "any", "memory", "of", "that", "awful", "day", "but", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "legacy", "of", "JFK", ",", "what", "would", "you", "think", "it", "should", "be", "as", "a", "member", "of", "the", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well you know I think that he was a man who really loved our country and tried to make our policy both domestically and internationally reflective of our greatest values of Democracy of caring about people who live in poverty of making sure that everyone in our country actually had a vote and was able to go to the polls and vote.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "you", "know", "I", "think", "that", "he", "was", "a", "man", "who", "really", "loved", "our", "country", "and", "tried", "to", "make", "our", "policy", "both", "domestically", "and", "internationally", "reflective", "of", "our", "greatest", "values", "of", "Democracy", "of", "caring", "about", "people", "who", "live", "in", "poverty", "of", "making", "sure", "that", "everyone", "in", "our", "country", "actually", "had", "a", "vote", "and", "was", "able", "to", "go", "to", "the", "polls", "and", "vote", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["JFK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Amazing, Kerry we got this, this fabulous pictures an iconic image is you playing hide and seek inside the Oval Office with President Kennedy there, with Caroline I think it was wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Amazing", ",", "Kerry", "we", "got", "this", ",", "this", "fabulous", "pictures", "an", "iconic", "image", "is", "you", "playing", "hide", "and", "seek", "inside", "the", "Oval", "Office", "with", "President", "Kennedy", "there", ",", "with", "Caroline", "I", "think", "it", "was", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Yeah, that's the two of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "two", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oval Office"], "PERSON": ["Kerry", "Kennedy", "Caroline"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "When you see that picture what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "that", "picture", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Well it just brings back so much joy of my youngest years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "just", "brings", "back", "so", "much", "joy", "of", "my", "youngest", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Is there a plan for the family to get together?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "plan", "for", "the", "family", "to", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Well you know, our family really tries to celebrate his birthday and not his day of death.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "you", "know", ",", "our", "family", "really", "tries", "to", "celebrate", "his", "birthday", "and", "not", "his", "day", "of", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Is there anybody in the family as you look at it do you think could genuinely have the political drive and aspiration to perhaps one day run for President?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anybody", "in", "the", "family", "as", "you", "look", "at", "it", "do", "you", "think", "could", "genuinely", "have", "the", "political", "drive", "and", "aspiration", "to", "perhaps", "one", "day", "run", "for", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "TO", "RB", "CD", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Well I don't know what the future is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "future", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "How do you see a breakthrough?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "see", "a", "breakthrough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "I think that, you know, first of all let me just say that you have been so fantastic on this issue and really no one has been a greater advocate for than you have so I want to thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "first", "of", "all", "let", "me", "just", "say", "that", "you", "have", "been", "so", "fantastic", "on", "this", "issue", "and", "really", "no", "one", "has", "been", "a", "greater", "advocate", "for", "than", "you", "have", "so", "I", "want", "to", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "In terms of what Robert Kennedy said there, that actually the real legacy of John F. Kennedy may well be that he was a man of peace during a time of great conflict, is that a fair analysis?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "what", "Robert", "Kennedy", "said", "there", ",", "that", "actually", "the", "real", "legacy", "of", "John", "F.", "Kennedy", "may", "well", "be", "that", "he", "was", "a", "man", "of", "peace", "during", "a", "time", "of", "great", "conflict", ",", "is", "that", "a", "fair", "analysis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "He was a man of peace but he was a cold war hawk.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "man", "of", "peace", "but", "he", "was", "a", "cold", "war", "hawk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Kennedy", "John F. Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Was he a villain or potentially trying to be the hero of this particular war by stopping it before it really happened?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "a", "villain", "or", "potentially", "trying", "to", "be", "the", "hero", "of", "this", "particular", "war", "by", "stopping", "it", "before", "it", "really", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well Piers we'll never know exactly what he would have done, he didn't know himself but it's clear to me from having read a mass of document that he had no desire to put massive numbers of ground troops into Vietnam.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "Piers", "we", "'ll", "never", "know", "exactly", "what", "he", "would", "have", "done", ",", "he", "did", "n't", "know", "himself", "but", "it", "'s", "clear", "to", "me", "from", "having", "read", "a", "mass", "of", "document", "that", "he", "had", "no", "desire", "to", "put", "massive", "numbers", "of", "ground", "troops", "into", "Vietnam", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Do you subscribe to any of the conspiracy theories?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "subscribe", "to", "any", "of", "the", "conspiracy", "theories", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "ASSASSINATION OF JOHN F. KENNEDY: No I don't Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["ASSASSINATION", "OF", "JOHN", "F.", "KENNEDY", ":", "No", "I", "do", "n't", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren Commission"]}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Yeah Doug Brinkley, do you concur?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", "Doug", "Brinkley", ",", "do", "you", "concur", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Yeah I largely concur, I think the Warren Commission got an awful lot right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "I", "largely", "concur", ",", "I", "think", "the", "Warren", "Commission", "got", "an", "awful", "lot", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Doug Brinkley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CD", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Where do you lie?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "lie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well I think he was, he was not a great President, he was there for only a thousand days, six briefest presidency on the country's history, well I think he's certainly a significant president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "think", "he", "was", ",", "he", "was", "not", "a", "great", "President", ",", "he", "was", "there", "for", "only", "a", "thousand", "days", ",", "six", "briefest", "presidency", "on", "the", "country", "'s", "history", ",", "well", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "certainly", "a", "significant", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "He can affect people so much around the world?", "question_tokens": ["He", "can", "affect", "people", "so", "much", "around", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Yes, yes exactly Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "exactly", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John F. Kennedy"], "LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Would he had survived being the kind of president a man that he was in the modern media environment?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "had", "survived", "being", "the", "kind", "of", "president", "a", "man", "that", "he", "was", "in", "the", "modern", "media", "environment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "It would have been quite difficult but Kennedy has the advantage in history, we're all getting older, all of your viewers but John F. Kennedy is always the handsome statesman, president gunned down in his prime.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "been", "quite", "difficult", "but", "Kennedy", "has", "the", "advantage", "in", "history", ",", "we", "'re", "all", "getting", "older", ",", "all", "of", "your", "viewers", "but", "John", "F.", "Kennedy", "is", "always", "the", "handsome", "statesman", ",", "president", "gunned", "down", "in", "his", "prime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "We've got 10 days or so to the Anniversary itself but how should he be remembered?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "got", "10", "days", "or", "so", "to", "the", "Anniversary", "itself", "but", "how", "should", "he", "be", "remembered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Well, he should be remembered as a significant, important president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "should", "be", "remembered", "as", "a", "significant", ",", "important", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]